<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Rachel Manderfeld, Portfolio</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Rachel Manderfeld, Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moonrayspex.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chiniguchi Waterways Provincial Park Canoe Route Map</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/cwpp_map/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 20:25:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/cwpp_map/</guid><description>Map created using Ontario datasets in ArcGIS Pro and Mapublisher for AI.</description></item><item><title>Lake Explorer for Peterborough and the Kawarthas</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/lake_explorer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 19:25:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/lake_explorer/</guid><description>Scope of project is lakes in Peterborough and the Kawarthas. Designed for general and citizen-scientist users. Made as part of collaborative final project for GIS program at Fleming College in partnership with Kawartha Conservation.
Teammates include L. Greidanus and K. Jones-McGowan.
View Lake Explorer
Images from website:</description></item><item><title>Kootenay Valley Remote Sensing Image Analysis</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/remote_sensing_kootenay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 12:50:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/remote_sensing_kootenay/</guid><description>Three different methods of image analysis using Catalyst (PCI Geomatica): Pansharpened True Colour Composite, SWIR, Standard False Colour Composite.</description></item><item><title>Ranked Habitat Analysis for Salamanders</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/salamander/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 12:50:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/salamander/</guid><description>Ranked habitat analysis using suitable landcover, ideal elevations, and transportation interference in the area between Lindsay and Peterborough, Ontario. Datasets from Geospatial Data Canada, iNaturalist, and SOLRIS. Co-collaborator with L. Greidanus.</description></item><item><title>Supervised Classification of Oak Ridges Morraine</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/oak_ridges/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 12:50:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/oak_ridges/</guid><description>Supervised classification of orthophotography using PCI Geomatica / Catalyst of the Oak Ridges Morraine area.</description></item><item><title>Modelling Canopy Height Model with LiDAR and Photogrammetric-derived Point Clouds</title><link>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/lidar_chm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 03:25:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://moonrayspex.github.io/projects/creations/lidar_chm/</guid><description>Imagery derived from elevation classified photogrammetric-derived elevation point cloud layer.
Source image from Ontario GeoHub of a 1 km 2 area near Bailieboro, Ontario. Image initially overlayed on standard false colour composite of an orthophotographic image of the same area from 2013 (not shown).
Figure 1. Below: Bailieboro LiDAR (sensor and date of acquisition) DSM (Digital Surface Model) shown in shaded relief.
DSM derived from elevation point cloud layer. Forest, hedge rows and powerlines are prominent.</description></item></channel></rss>